[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the game of Scrabble, if a player uses all seven of their letters in a turn, they receive a bonus of how many points?", "correct_answer": "50", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "100", "25"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the highest waterfall in North America?", "correct_answer": "James Bruce Falls", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard Brown Falls", "Johnathan Stevens Falls", "John Cliff Falls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In nature, fungi are known tp form symbiotic relationships with which of these organisms?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Plants", "Algae", "Insects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the popular slogan of the Colorado Gold Rush?", "correct_answer": "Pikes Peak or Bust", "incorrect_answers": ["Westward Ho", "Colorado Gold to Go", "Go West Young Men"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the only Top 40 hit of musician, bandleader, and television impresario Lawrence Welk?", "correct_answer": "Calcutta", "incorrect_answers": ["Theme from Exodus", "Telstar", "Old Cape Cod"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was first sail the length of the Amazon River and it was on this voyage that the Amazon got its name.", "correct_answer": "Francisco de Orellana", "incorrect_answers": ["Pascal", "Francisco Pizarro", "de Gassett"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many of the AFI Top Ten American films are also listed among the top 100 titles rented by Netflix subscribers?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "5", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of symptoms do parasite infections usually induce in humans?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Joint pain", "Chronic fatigue", "Unrestrained hunger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about storing peaches?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Storing peaches for ripening is useless.", "Refrigeration is not recommended.", "Peaches should be stored at room temperature."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the word for fear of horses?", "correct_answer": "Equinophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Ereuthrophobia", "Eremophobia", "Epistemophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet is 5th from the sun?", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Saturn", "Mars", "Earth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name does Chuck give to the volleyball in the movie Cast Away?", "correct_answer": "Wilson", "incorrect_answers": ["William", "Albert", "Bill"]}]